Threatened by a ruthless demon, humanity was on the brink of destruction.
All seemed lost until a lone mage stepped forward and took up the fight.
After his triumph, he was hailed as the Wizard King, and his story became legend.
Following their battle at the Underwater Temple, Yami, Asta, Charmy, and Finral reported to the Wizard King. But then...
Please forgive the intrusion, sir. It's Kitan, a border village in sight of frequent skirmishes with the Diamonds Kingdom. A diamond unit is attacking it as we speak!
Whoa! That looks like a whole army of them!
Three of the eight Shining Generals.
The eight Shining Generals? I've never heard of them before!
They're the eight most powerful people in the whole Diamond Kingdom. You might think of them as being kinda like our Magic Knight Captains.
One squad rushed to Kitan's aid in this critical time of need.
Wait, hold on! Is that...
The mightiest Magic Knight Squad in the Clover Kingdom!
The Golden Dawn!
Nothing done!
Yami and his knights quickly headed for Kai'un to provide additional backup.
Okay, Yuno. I'm coming!
By the time we're done, those Diamond Kingdom mages will regret ever setting foot in our country.
Oh, that's so pretty!
What happened to me today?
Hey!
That's right now.
whealue of you!
If you wish for a new one, this is a Dame 858The
Thank you.
誰かのためじゃない 今はまだ 自分に追いつくまで
かむしゃらでじめき飛ばした 体中の声が 翼広げて
どんな未来も迷うよ 風吹きて 自分を追い越すまで
誰かのためすると 日本語が interag Visit us!
Well, aren't you a couple of gorgeous ladies?
There's a hill nearby where some beautiful flowers grow.
Say, why don't you come take a romantic stroll with me and I'll show you.
What's wrong? You look like you're scared to death all of a sudden.
Shoot.
Hey! You sabotaged my date!
Shake it off!
You'll live. Now quit your complaining and help us get to chitin' already.
Huh? But I thought I had the day off!
Did you really just say what I think you said, you little lowlife?
You'll get a day off when you're dead, you understand?
Woo! Finral! Let's do this!
Now you better open up that portal before I open one in your skull!
Then there'll be no getting out of it this time!
I'm scared! Come on, you're our only hope!
Whoa, I wouldn't go that far!
What? I don't think I understand what's going on anymore!
Clock's tickin'!
Okay, okay, I'll get right on it!
It's the Golden Dawn!
Ha ha ha!
So this kid must be the advanced guard for the Golden Dawn!
I gotta say, you're not bad for a puny brat!
How tragic.
Behavior like yours is terribly unbecoming for a member of the eight shining generals.
It's embarrassing.
Lagos!
Let me help you. I can't bear to watch.
Don't go stickin' your nose into this! I want to kill him!
The townspeople seem awfully confident in you.
What the hell! Aren't you listening to me?
Alright. Let's see how well you defend yourself and all of them!
Arrows. Bells.
Right here? Leave it to me!
Wind magic. Swift white. Bow.
What the...?
That's absurd! You deflected my arrows so swiftly and broke the barrier!
You wanted to find out if I could defend myself, right? Well, can you?
Damn, who is this boy?
I can protect myself and all my friends.
You heard him! You know when I are one soul. Isn't that right?
Uh, hello? Not gonna respond? Could you at least give me a quick yes or no?
No.
You know what? I changed my mind! I need an explanation!
I bet you want me to help now, don't you, Lagos?
How dared that little upstart make a fool of me? I'll handle him myself.
Out of my way, Brox!
I told you before! Leave the twerp to me!
He's mine!
No, he's mine!
He's mine, I said!
I saw him first!
What are you talking about? You know belongs to me!
Idiots.
Look at that.
He's gotten so much stronger since we first met inside that dungeon.
It's a crying shame how fast they grow up.
Makes me feel like an old man.
It's the same way with my own little girls.
I remember they used to say,
Someday we're gonna marry our daddy.
These days they act like they're all embarrassed of me.
They won't even let me wash my underwear with their clothes.
General Lotus?
They say, leave us alone daddy, you have onion breath.
Now, steal creation magic, fear spiral less!
Damn, there's so many!
This is bad. They've got us outnumbered.
That's it, you weaklings! Keep on struggling!
This magic is clinging to us. It makes it so our spells don't work properly!
Here!
It's Mucca's creation magic, known as Mucca Snail.
A powerful spell that dramatically reduces the abilities of anyone it touches.
You can find it all you want, but there's no escape!
Caring to see pitiful fools like you, writhing in agony.
Oh, it's such a thrill!
Wow, that looks like it's a tough spell to beat.
Or rather it would be, if it wasn't completely useless against me.
What kind of attack is that?
Spatial magic?
Right. That's the problem with this spell. It destroys everything.
That's too bad. I guess someone will just have to rebuild it, won't they?
Interesting. I'm pretty sure that guy's the leader of the Golden Dawn.
Why's he just standing there? Kinda creepy.
He's got his grimoire open, so I assume he's using magic of some sort, but...
All I can see is what looks like a bunch of tree roots.
Maybe he's gonna grow a tree.
That's a peaceful thing to do.
Must be nice to have strong enough magic to make something that protects a whole village.
Is he absorbing people's magic?
Why am I always the one to notice things?
Listen, you three. This is Lotus. The enemy captain from the Golden Dawn seems to be preparing to launch a large-scale magic attack.
Its range will span all of Kitan at least. I repeat, look at their captain.
He's preparing for a large-scale magic attack.
I guess I should run then.
The time is at hand. Behold, the great tree grows.
What kind of insane power does this Golden Dawn guy have?
World tree magic. Great Mistiltane tree.
All for the good of the Clover Kingdom.
World tree magic.
So this is Kitan. Wait.
Was there a giant tree in the middle of it?
How'd they build their whole town around that?
You bet it grows giant fruit, too.
I've heard enough out of you two idiots.
Hmm. Looks like Goldy Guts work.
Huh? You mean this is a spell?
Seems like they've got it covered.
Oh good. Then we can go back now, right?
Nah. I want to see how the fight's going.
Huh?
I'm guessing the captain's at the top of the tree.
I'm gonna head up now.
You go help the civilians.
Oh, and try not to die.
Yes, sir!
Hey, wait!
How long is this gonna take?
Before we do anything, I gotta get some of that fruit.
Musta's already injured. And Charmy's… well, she's just Charmy. Doesn't look good for me.
Goodness. It appears there was a massive amount of power on the battlefield. Fortunately, I think this cleared most of it.
Our army's been wiped out.
It can't be. How did we lose so many soldiers? I'll kill you!
You shouldn't be greedy, young man. It's not a good look for you.
My arms don't work, but I can still fight!
Hey, guys! There's a way out over here!
Step onto these, okay?
You're not hurt, are you, miss? Here, allow me.
Thanks so much for your help.
We're Magic Knights, so it's our duty to protect the Clover Kingdom from danger.
Hey, after this, why don't we go out for some tea? Sound good?
Uh-oh. Chin up. Don't cry!
Huh?
That's strange. Someone's fighting one of their guys solo up there.
That's Yuno!
Careful, my prince!
Go! Go! P-O-P!
When you win, please bring some food to me! Yeah!
Yeah!
Ugh!
Huh?
I had no idea he was this strong.
But as a Shining General, I won't be beaten.
You will surrender to my beautiful magic!
Who cares about that, dude?
Beauty doesn't mean a thing during battle.
To win, you have to be strong.
It's so beautiful.
The Noctumel with one spell!
Ah, the winds of love. My sweet prince.
Thought I saw a familiar speck down here.
So what brings you to Kitan?
Asta.
That guy joined the Magic Knights when Asta did.
And why are you scrambling around looking all beaten up and covered in sweat?
So gross.
He worked his way up to the Golden Dawn Elite?
A guy like him makes the Black Bulls look wimpy.
Plus he's handsome.
Bet he's popular too.
If you got those injuries while fighting someone like I think you did, then that must mean you got stronger again.
I won't lose. Got that?
Huh?
Is he smiling?
Wow. Such a great smile.
I could have a hundred helpings of it and still be asking for more?
Not just me. Looks like you've gotten more powerful too.
But I won't lose either. No way!
So he's a Golden Dawn Elite with good looks for days and his magic abilities off the charts?
But he's competing with Asta. A member of the Black Bulls who's a total meathead. With no magic.
Seems like those two make pretty good rivals.
There you are, Yuno!
Thank goodness you're not injured.
And Asta too?
It is him!
But what happened to your arms?
Let's see. Does it hurt when I do this?
Of course I didn't ask you that because I'm worried or anything.
You should have never let your guard down, fool.
Uh, sorry?
Here. I'll use my healing magic.
I'll be fine. You should probably take care of the villagers instead.
You're right! I shouldn't have been so forward! Please forgive me!
Precisely. We don't have time to deal with you, Asta.
Mimosa!
Ready!
You two should stay together for now.
I'm sure it's difficult to fight without your arms.
Not that I'm coddling you or anything.
You can leave now.
Bye, Asta!
Please take care!
Bye!
See ya!
Well, well, well.
So that's where you were.
You must be the Golden Dawn's captain.
I underestimated you. This is some serious magic power you've got.
Yes, and I could say the same about you as well.
You shouldn't die in vain. Take your comrades and leave this land.
What did you say to me?
Diamond soldiers don't retreat, no matter the circumstance.
Never!
Red Clay creation magic! Brilliant armor!
Heavy artillery!
That was pathetic! Was that supposed to be painful?
Ha ha ha ha ha ha! Let me guess. You've already run out of magic.
World Tree Magic. Mistiltane Seed.
You should be honored, you know.
Your magic is being used for the nourishment of the Clover Kingdom.
It's an ambush. He must have concealed his power.
Yami!
That's my name. Good to see you, Featherface.
Ouch. I thought I could turn things around if I bag the Golden Dawn Captain.
But I guess not.
Who could have expected I'd have to fight this guy again?
And he's even stronger than the last time.
Kinda makes me feel like a pitiful old man.
Think this means you owe me one, Vongence.
Thank you for saving me.
So, you read his key. Impressive.
Hey, old Diamond guy I don't know.
You ready to surrender now?
Oh, come on. You forgot?
Here, look.
I'm not interested in your nasty man chest, pal.
I'll cut you down.
Harsh.
You want to fight? Come at me.
This is a tricky situation for me.
Which means...
I should handle it the Diamond way.
Retreat!
Well, he's decisive. Good.
Now, that's done.
The view's pretty nice up here, and it's just the two of us.
How about we have a little chat?
You got time?
You know, it takes some serious strength to pull off a spell like this one.
Please. It's only possible thanks to my enemies.
So, World Tree Magic.
Is that the only kind you got?
Nothing else?
I'm sorry.
What are you implying, Yami?
Well, I'm the kind of guy who goes with his gut instinct.
Vangeance, if you don't mind.
Lose the mask.
You don't mind.
Thank you.
恋だろう 恋だろう 謎は僕らが通り越して
まだ名前などない その輝きを
己の中に見つけるんでしょ
天上天下 みな 唯一がドッグソング
ここはここにいるってことで
あれでもない これでもない 今この瞬間 生まれた人
どこでいても 変わらないでも
いやいやいや いやいやいや
不当たり前なの 何もんの手もないもの
生きちゃって そこだって 僕は僕でいたいの
ようやくドッグソング
徹沢山夜
七回生のチャレ ju l 私は
No, for the universe full of die-hard Charmy Pappits and fans out there.
We're going to answer your prayers and show you all the adorable Charmy moments you've been dying to see.
I'm ready!
Number one, Charmy the Wonderer.
Number two, Festival Charmy!
Number three, Happy Birthday, Charmy!
Number four, Charmy the Thunder God!
Number five, Charmy the Alien!
Finally, number six, Merlion Charmy!
So cool!
I thought there were seven.
Did you see that, Asta?
I've gotten incredibly strong since the last time we met.
I won't lose to you in strength, good looks, or in height.
Black Clover, page 53, Behind the Mask.
I'm the one who will become the Wizard King.
I've gotten a libro, too.
I've gotten a fingerprint, and I can long resume you then.
Then, what's going on here?
Let me record!
I'm not going to record!
I'm getting một cu-là disappointingêmes in thys
which has two öğretries.
So, let's incorporate!
I don't get half a vraag, but let me alsoar-